[
    {
        "QID": "1",
        "question": "This refers to the way something feels, or looks as if they might feel like something.",
        "answer-1": "Space",
        "answer-2": "Line",
        "answer-3": "Shape",
        "answer-4": "Texture",
        "correct": "Texture"
    },
    {
        "QID": "2",
        "question": "When lines meet to form an enclosed area this is formed.",
        "answer-1": "Shadow",
        "answer-2": "Form",
        "answer-3": "Shape",
        "answer-4": "Texture",
        "correct": "Shape"
    },
    {
        "QID": "3",
        "question": "Mixing the colors blue and red in equal proportion will produce which of the following hues?",
        "answer-1": "Maroon",
        "answer-2": "Violet",
        "answer-3": "Orange",
        "answer-4": "Brown",
        "correct": "Violet"
    },
    {
        "QID": "4",
        "question": "Italian Baroque art developed primarily for which of the following purposes?",
        "answer-1": "Stimulating interest in the church",
        "answer-2": "Communicating the need for social justice",
        "answer-3": "Entertaining wealthy merchants",
        "answer-4": "Celebrating the architectural styles of classical antiquity",
        "correct": "Stimulating interest in the church"
    },
    {
        "QID": "5",
        "question": "Which of the following components of Gothic cathedrals would be useful to study in a physics class because it was designed to support outward force?",
        "answer-1": "Portal",
        "answer-2": "Stained Glass Window",
        "answer-3": "Flying Buttress",
        "answer-4": "Clerestory",
        "correct": "Flying Buttress"
    },
    {
        "QID": "6",
        "question": "Adding black to a color to make it darker creates a?",
        "answer-1": "Tint",
        "answer-2": "Secondary Color",
        "answer-3": "Shade",
        "answer-4": "Complementary Color",
        "correct": "Tint"
    },
    {
        "QID": "7",
        "question": "Objects found in the center of an art piece are in the?",
        "answer-1": "Background",
        "answer-2": "Foreground",
        "answer-3": "Middleground",
        "answer-4": "Horizon",
        "correct": "Foreground"
    },
    {
        "QID": "8",
        "question": "Colors located across from each other on the color wheel are called?",
        "answer-1": "Correlated",
        "answer-2": "Secondary",
        "answer-3": "Complementary",
        "answer-4": "Shades",
        "correct": "Complementary"
    },
    {
        "QID": "9",
        "question": "Who painted the art piece called: Wheatfield with Crows?",
        "answer-1": "Salvador Dali",
        "answer-2": "Van Gogh",
        "answer-3": "Andy Warhol",
        "answer-4": "Michelangelo",
        "correct": "Van Gogh"
    },
    {
        "QID": "10",
        "question": "Who famously had a blue period from 1901-1904?",
        "answer-1": "Rembrandt",
        "answer-2": "Salvador Dali",
        "answer-3": "Van Gogh",
        "answer-4": "Pablo Picasso",
        "correct": "Pablo Picasso"
    }
]
